Near michael runswick has been making the
round and saw lively and so on the mark
the least
The mark of the beast has
already been emilious
Ah but that when the dollar came out
And then
Upon the dollar came
Dollar came out so now
That ten dollar came out as a
mark where you have to live
I say somehow some way the
devil beast used the dollars
Or the marks and you die
could not worship them
We have already taken the mark
Then
Ay I and I idle
I don't
Say that
The mitigation for john meth
Was at the a to take our marks
And then once our marks are gone
there's no more act plans to grow
Now michael runswick has
been on me oxenous lately
And then
He thought he is a weird guy ah gone
a weird guise ah he was ayes again
When ay aye first
Came out everyone better like dada was a
terminator must come a determinator came
out and
And I write round of me have
athmatum me because I said
No way said I has gone chilles
As a berwickynamics
Ragonymics starts
Amer karama starts what is equal did
So people think
That the day I will kill them because it
is the super alien who super intelligence
superb land
By the energy
They say it superman but I say it's energy
Human
Half an
Evolving their girl at work
Ah many times some speculate
on how many times of men
Much longer
Than the fairy center has been
training at the day descent
And so it's not efficient because we
He is quant of energy
I whereas but there's a commergy
So this not even doro
dynamics is lesser his most
Or is
Not an energy
The heaths let off into gases is
While we take that heat in I should
goes into our ears on buds like we got
different things goin on
they just train up one thing
That's happened that the
Robar
Can never
Take on
The quanto
And the stated israel
A quaton is too many
The poplars when you watch a waterfall
fall down he sank he thanked energy right
Natasha's wrong
Right that is raw energy completely
different you know completely different in the
form of images use
Inside of a giron
But the amount of
Trick catalogs
As out of the water
It is like infinite comparative law
designed its stupid water bound
Highway